Señor, déjeme
break it down to you...
Our competitors...
They are like crazed gardeners,
you know?
Just growing skyscrapers of
glass and concrete.
But...
Aspen Corp is taking another
approach.
We...
We want to build suburban
family style hotels.
Because...
Isn't our main goal to spend
more quality time with our families?
Yeah.
It is.
How much
does it take to buy into this project
as the sole investor?
I can explain you everything
over lunch.
Because right now
it's your time with your kids.
Sorry, sweetheart.
I'm meeting with the senator at lunch.
How about
a late dinner?
Actually, we have to go back
to Baltimore tomorrow.
Yeah, the hotel association
is wrapping up the year with the party.
Here's the plan.
After we dine together,
you’ll stay here in the guest room.
And in the morning, my helicopter
will pick you up and take you
to Baltimore.
I'll make you coffee.
Perfect plan.
Thank you.